[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace_01A",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 9,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_AllyaMusa",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 9,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_EliasDerit",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 10,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_EliasDerit",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_07",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Response_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 10,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_08",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 10,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_alt",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 10,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Success_alt",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 10,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett_03",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_10",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Proposal_Prompt_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_05_RegentJinJae",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 11,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett_03",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_12",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT2_Footwear_15",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 12,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett_03",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_15",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_13",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT2_Legwear_15",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 12,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_15",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 13,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Moira_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_17",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "amuletmonarchsblufft3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 14,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Moira_03",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_18",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_17",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT2_Handwear_15",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 14,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_18",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_NPCGreet_Moira_07",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 15,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_20",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT2_Chestwear_15",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 15,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace_03",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_20",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 16,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen_01",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_22",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "HoningStoneT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_23_ToTower",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 16,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_23",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_22",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 16,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_23",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_destroyer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Warmonger",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_destroyer",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_musketeer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Musketeer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_musketeer",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_mystic",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Theurgist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_mystic",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_occultist",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Occultist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_occultist",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_ranger",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Tracker",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_ranger",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_soldier",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Mercenary",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_soldier",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_swordsman",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae_02",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_swordsman",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Headgear_20",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_alt",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Success_alt",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Headgear_20",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Start_Prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_FionaMurphy",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_02_GatherGift",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_EddaYonkers",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_03_CollectPicks",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_CemalQadir",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 9,
		"Task": "12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_AsheDubois_01",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_13",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 11,
		"Task": "12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_HugoMolina",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_07_ForgeRing",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 12,
		"Task": "12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_JeongNabi",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_08_GatherFangs",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 12,
		"Task": "12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_HamzaKillic",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_09_CollectGlass",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 14,
		"Task": "12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_OliviaBarovier",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_10_BreakCurse",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 14,
		"Task": "12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_HugoMolina_01",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 15,
		"Task": "12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_DayoMusa",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_AsheDubois",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21 && 12A_Side_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_13_DevilHoney",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_GeertieLother",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_14_CollectWine",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 9,
		"Task": "12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_GeertieLother",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_14",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_13",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_15_CollectResources",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_CemalQadir",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_15",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "12_CemalQadir",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_16",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_15",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Success",
		"ObjectiveReward": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Start_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 7,
		"Task": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12A_Side_17",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_16",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
		"Title": "@12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Obj_Title",
		"Description": "@12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Obj_Desc",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "1",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0101_downpayment_MB",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 14,
		"Task": "1225_0101a_d_00_container_downpayment",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoChason",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
		"AchievementId": "S_downpayment",
		"ItemRewardName": "QuestRewardHousing1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0101_downpayment_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_complete_available_response_a",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0101_downpayment_FL",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 14,
		"Task": "1225_0101d_d_00_container_downpayment",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoChason",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
		"AchievementId": "S_downpayment",
		"ItemRewardName": "QuestRewardHousing1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0101_downpayment_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_complete_available_response_a",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0101_downpayment_EF",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 14,
		"Task": "1225_0101c_d_00_container_downpayment",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoChason",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
		"AchievementId": "S_downpayment",
		"ItemRewardName": "QuestRewardHousing1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0101_downpayment_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_complete_available_response_a",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0101_downpayment_WW",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 14,
		"Task": "1225_0101d_d_00_container_downpayment",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoChason",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
		"AchievementId": "S_downpayment",
		"ItemRewardName": "QuestRewardHousing1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0101_downpayment_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0101_downpayment_complete_available_response_a",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0201_majorpurchase",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 18,
		"Task": "1225_0201_d_00_container_majorpurchase",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoChason",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_2",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "S_downpayment",
		"ItemRewardName": "House_HousingItem_Chair_Settler_Chair01_A",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_complete_available_response",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 21,
		"Task": "1225_0301_d_00_container_insuringinvestmentA",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoTravelersA",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_3a",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_complete_available_response",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 23,
		"Task": "1225_0302_d_00_container_insuringinvestmentB",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoTravelersA",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_3b",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_3a",
		"ItemRewardName": "House_HousingItem_Storage_T1_ChestOldLog",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_complete_available_response_a",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0401_siteinspection",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 30,
		"Task": "1225_0401_d_00_container_siteinspection",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoTravelersA",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_4",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_3b",
		"ItemRewardName": "House_HousingItem_Bed_Settler_Bed02_A",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0401_siteinspection_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0401_siteinspection_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0401_siteinspection_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0401_siteinspection_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0401_siteinspection_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0401_siteinspection_complete_available_response",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 37,
		"Task": "1225_0501_d_00_container_mandatoryimprovements",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoTravelersB",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_5",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_complete_available_response_a",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1225_0601_closingcost",
		"Type": "SkillProgression",
		"DifficultyLevel": 50,
		"Task": "1225_0601_d_00_container_closingcost",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1225_GiacomoTravelersB",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_6",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_Housing_5",
		"ItemRewardName": "QuestRewardHousing7",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@1225_0601_closingcost_objective_title",
		"Description": "@1225_0601_closingcost_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1225_0601_closingcost_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1225_0601_closingcost_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1225_0601_closingcost_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1225_0601_closingcost_complete_available_response",
		"RewardWithPlayerLevel": true,
		"RewardType": "Quest+"
	}
]